

COSIMO SIMONE FARALLO

亩 29/03/1998

9

Milano(MI)

CONTACT

Address:

Viale Famagosta 21, Milano (MI)

• **Phone**: 3391953659

• E-mail:

simonefarallo@gmail.com

• Linkedin: in/simone-farallo

SUMMARY

Current student in the faculty of Data science at University of Milano-Bicocca, specializing in data management and analysis to support decision-making in various work environments.

Use of statistical models, decision models and machine learning for problem solving.

Construction of recommendation systems and databases in the university environment.

HARD SKILL

Work environment

- Microsoft office package: Word, Excel, PowerPoint
- ERP System
- CiaoTicket
- Canva

Education enviroment

- Database operation: SQL, Neo4j
- Statistical Operation: R, Python
- Others: KNIME, Silk , Protege, Tableau

SOFT SKILL

- Dynamic and rational in decision making
- Problem solving
- Project managment
- Organisational capability
- · Results oriented
- Good manners and open to work in a group.

EXPERIENCE

- IT employee, Noi energia srl (Energy & Gas company), Molfetta(BA) | 2019- 2021
- Management of logistical activities of the outgoing correspondence.
- Checking outgoing invoices and quality control of postage.
- IT employee, Molfetta Calcio (Football club), Molfetta(BA) | 2019- 2020
- Management and organization of sports events.
- Responsible for ticket sales.
- Management of single event reports.
- Organizer and runner (Private company), Molfetta(BA) | 2016-2020
- Management and organization of musical events.
- Sales and rescounts of tickcets.
- Management of food and drink areas.
- Waiter (Restaurants and American bars),
 Molfetta(BA), Milano(MI) | 2016- current

EDUCATION

University of Milano Bicocca- Milano Master's degree | 2021 - current

• Data Science

University of Bari Aldo Moro - Bari Bachelor's degree | 2017 - 2021

• Statistical science

I.I.S.S. "G. Ferraris" - Molfetta Secondary school | 2012 - 2017

· Technological secondary school

LANGUAGES

• English - B1

PORTFOLIO

GitHub: https://github.com/SimoneFarallo

Autorizzo il trattamento dei dati personali presenti nel CV ai sensi del D.Lgs. 2018/101 e del GDPR (Regolamento UE 2016/679).